stack.com 2019-05-05

# Get Bigger, Stronger, Better, Faster | STACK

STACK, Inc. ("STACK") recognizes that its customers, visitors, Members, and others who use [http://www.stack.com](http://www.stack.com/) or other web sites owned or operated by STACK (the "STACK Websites") (collectively or individually "Members") value their privacy. This Privacy Policy details important information regarding the use and disclosure of Member information collected on the STACK Websites. STACK provides this Privacy Policy to help you make an informed decision about whether to use or continue using the STACK Websites. 

This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and is subject to the STACK Terms of Use found at [http://www.stack.com/terms-of-use/](http://www.stack.com/terms-of-use). Your use of the STACK Websites and any personal information you provide on the STACK Websites remains subject to the terms of this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use. 

Please note that any video, image, or other content posted at the direction of Members onto the STACK Websites becomes published content and is not considered personally identifiable information subject to this Privacy Policy. 

## Member Information Collected by STACK

### Personally Identifiable Information

You provide certain personally identifiable information (such as your name and email address) to STACK when choosing to participate in various activities on the STACK Websites such as registering, creating a public profile, uploading videos, posting messages, entering contests or sweepstakes, taking advantage of promotions, responding to surveys, watching videos, or subscribing to newsletters or other mailing lists.

Our properties may feature Nielsen proprietary measurement software, which will allow you to contribute to market research, such as Nielsen TV Ratings. To learn more about the information that Nielsen software may collect and your choices with regard to it, please see the Nielsen Digital Measurement Privacy Policy at <http://www.nielsen.com/digitalprivacy>.

### Cookies Information

STACK logs standard Member information and clickstream data for all Members, including a Member's IP operating system, and page views. When Members visit particular pages within STACK, a Member ID may be placed in the URL, allowing customized features for the Member. Members should be aware that other websites visited before entering STACK might place personally identifiable information within a Member's URL during a visit to their website, and STACK has no control over such websites. Accordingly, some of this information may be logged by a subsequent website that collects URL information. In addition to the standard log information, STACK may use a variety of technologies to create a more personalized experience for its Members. We may also use cookies to enable customizable content for Members, as they become available. Members have the option, within their Internet browsers, to disable cookies and continue to access the STACK Website. Pixel tags are tiny graphic files that are included in HTML-encoded e-mail messages. STACK may use pixel tags to gather information about the e-mails we send to our registered Members. STACK web pages may also contain similar pixel tags that allow us to count Members who have visited those pages, to compile aggregated statistics about site usage, and to deliver co-branded services as they become available. STACK pixel tags collect only a limited set of information including a cookie number, time and date of a page view, and a description of the page on which the pixel tag resides. STACK web pages may also contain pixel tags placed there by third party ad servers, to monitor the effectiveness of their advertising.

## How STACK Uses the Member Information

### Personally Identifiable Information

If you submit personally identifiable information to us through the STACK Websites, then we use your personal information to operate, maintain, and provide to you the features and functionality of the STACK Websites. Any personal information or video content that you voluntarily disclose online (within your public profile page, in messages and posting areas, etc.) becomes publicly available and can be collected and used by others. Your account name (not your email address) is displayed to other Members when they view your profile and when you upload videos or send messages through STACK Websites and other Members can contact you through your profile, messages and comments. Any videos that you submit to the STACK Websites may be redistributed through the internet and other media channels, and may be viewed by the general public. We do not use your email address or other personally identifiable information to send commercial or marketing messages without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out. We may, however, use your email address without further consent for non-marketing or administrative purposes (such as notifying you of major STACK Website changes or for customer service purposes).

### Cookies Information

We use both your personally identifiable information and certain non-personally-identifiable information (such as anonymous Member usage data, cookies, IP addresses, browser type, clickstream data, etc.) to improve the quality and design of the STACK Websites and to create new features, promotions, functionality, and services by storing, tracking, and analyzing Member preferences and trends. We may use cookies to save Member IDs, session validators, and on Member's browsers and hard drives, and may use them to provide tailored products or services to those Members, as they become available. We also may cross-match Member information with information collected from cookies and clickstream data in order to test features of the STACK Website, and to better personalize our various offerings for Members. IP addresses may be disclosed to a third party if we believe in good faith that the law or legal process so requires, or to protect the rights or property of STACK or others. From time to time we may extend various offers from various partner companies, including news or additional details on products and services. A Member's usage history may result in specifically tailored special offer screens or products. We may also produce aggregate reports for advertisers. This information will not include personally identifiable information about a Member, or a specific Member's online usage patterns.

### Third Party Tracking and Online Advertising

We may permit third party ad networks, social media companies, and other third party services to collect information about browsing behavior from visitors to our Service through cookies, social plug-ins, or other tracking technology. We may permit third party online advertising networks to collect information about your use of our websites over time so that they may play or display ads that may be relevant to your interests on our Service as well as on other websites or services. Typically, the information is collected through cookies or similar tracking technologies. The only way to completely “opt out” of the collection of any information through cookies or other tracking technology is to actively manage the settings on your browser or mobile device. Please refer to your browser’s or mobile device’s technical information for instructions on how to delete and disable cookies, and other tracking/recording tools. (To learn more about cookies, clear gifs/web beacons and related technologies and how you may opt-out of some of this tracking, you may wish to visit [http://www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/) and/or the Network Advertising Initiative’s online resources, at [http://optout.networkadvertising.org](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/). Depending on your mobile device, you may not be able to control tracking technologies through settings.

### Profile Information

STACK allows Members to provide information to a profile that is accessible to other Members. We use this profile information for the purposes of providing our services to you, such as to analyze demographics, to better personalize our various offerings for Members, or to enable other Members to find your profile. All information, including any personally identifiable information, which is disclosed by Members in his or her public profile and journal entries are available for others to see. We caution you not to share sensitive information (such as social security numbers, credit card numbers, and driver's license numbers) with other Members whom you do not know or place such information in your profile.

### Invitations

The New Member Invite feature is an easy way for Members to invite friends through email. The email address(es) that you supply to use this service will only be used to send invitations to join the STACK Websites.

### Surveys and Contests

At various times we may offer surveys or contests to Members. Surveys may ask for contact, demographic or unique identifying information to increase the value of the results. Contests may require contact information or other demographic or personally identifiable information in order to determine eligibility. STACK may use information collected from surveys and contests for the entertainment of Members, and to determine, notify and contact winners of various contests. In addition, Member's demographic and/or personally identifiable information and responses to survey and contest questions may be used by STACK and/or shared with third parties in order to provide specifically tailored special offers or advertisements. STACK will not share a Member's email address with third parties unless the Member specifically opts-in to such sharing during the completion of or registration for a survey or contest.

## When STACK Discloses the Member Information

We provide personally identifiable information and non-personally-identifiable information to our subsidiaries, affiliated companies, or other businesses or persons for the purpose of processing such information on our behalf. We require that these parties agree to process such information in compliance with our privacy policy, and we use reasonable efforts to limit their use of such information and to use other appropriate confidentiality and security measures. We do not share your personally identifiable information (such as name or email address) with other, third-party companies for their commercial or marketing use without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out. We do share non-personally-identifiable information (such as anonymous Member usage data, referring / exit pages and URLs, clickstream data, platform types, etc.) with interested third-parties to assist them in understanding the usage patterns for certain content, services, advertisements, promotions, and/or functionality on the STACK Websites. 

We may release personally identifiable information and/or non-personally-identifiable information if required to do so by law, or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with state and federal laws (such as U.S. Copyright Law) or respond to a court order, subpoena, or search warrant. STACK also reserves the right to disclose personally identifiable information and/or non-personally-identifiable information that STACK believes, in good faith, is appropriate or necessary to enforce our Terms of Use, take precautions against liability, to investigate and defend itself against any third-party claims or allegations, to assist government enforcement agencies, to protect the security or integrity of our web site, and to protect the rights, property, or personal safety of STACK, our Members or others. 

## Member Choices

Members may decline to submit personally identifiable information through the STACK Websites, in which case STACK may not be able to provide certain services to Members. Members may update or correct their personal profile information and email preferences at any time by visiting their My Profile page. Please note that media files uploaded by Members to the STACK Websites cannot be removed and remain subject to our Terms of Use. 

To protect your privacy and security, we take reasonable steps (such as requesting a unique password) to verify your identity before granting you profile access or making corrections. You are responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your unique password and account information at all times. 

Please contact STACK with any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, your personal information, your consent, or your opt-in or opt-out choices by visiting the following page <http://www.stack.com/contact-us/>. 

## Third-Party Links and Ad Servers

STACK allows other companies, called third-party ad servers or ad networks, to serve advertisements within the STACK Websites. These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to send, directly to your browser, the advertisements and links that appear on the STACK Websites. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. 

STACK does not provide any personally identifiable information to these third-party ad servers or ad networks without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out. However, please note that if an advertiser asks STACK to show an advertisement to a certain audience or audience segment and you respond to that advertisement, the advertiser or ad-server may conclude that you fit the description of the audience they are trying to reach. The advertiser may also use information regarding your use of the STACK Websites, such as the number of times you viewed an ad to determine which ads to deliver to you. 

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers or ad networks (see links below) for more information on their practices and for instructions on how to opt-out of certain practices. STACK's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. 

Currently, STACK has relationships with the following third-party ad servers or ad networks:   
**24/7 Real Media, Inc.** | <http://www.247realmedia.com/privacy.html>   
**DoubleClick** | <http://www.doubleclick.net/us/corporate/privacy>

## Data Security

STACK uses commercially reasonable physical, managerial, and technical safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of your personal information. We cannot, however, ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to STACK and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission of information, STACK makes commercially reasonable efforts to ensure the security of our systems. However, please note that this is not a guarantee that such information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical, or managerial safeguards. 

If STACK learns of a security systems breach, then we may attempt to notify you electronically so that you can take appropriate protective steps. STACK may post a notice on the STACK Websites if a security breach occurs. Depending on where you live, you may have a legal right to receive notice of a security breach in writing. 

## Children's' Privacy

STACK does not knowingly collect or maintain personally identifiable information or non-personally-identifiable information on the STACK Websites from persons under 13 years of age, and no part of our website is directed to persons under 13. If you are under 13 years of age, then please do not use or access the STACK Websites at any time or in any manner. If STACK learns that personally identifiable information of persons under 13 years of age has been collected on the STACK Websites without verified parental consent, then STACK will take the appropriate steps to delete this information. 

## International Members

The STACK service is available only to Members who have a valid postal address in the United States. 

## Change of Ownership

In the event of a change in ownership, or a direct merger or acquisition with another entity, we reserve the right to transfer all of STACK's Member information, including email addresses and postal addresses, to a separate entity. All registered Members will be notified of any change in ownership, merger or acquisition of STACK's assets by a third party, and may choose to modify any of their registration information at that time. 

## Revisions to Privacy Policy

STACK reserves the right to revise, amend, or modify this policy and our other policies and agreements at any time and in any manner. Notice of any revision, amendment, or modification will be posted on the website, and a Member's continued use of STACK will signify agreement to such changes. 

## Contacting STACK

Members with questions about this Privacy Policy and any of the aforementioned statements may contact STACK at privacy@stackmag.com or STACK, 1228 Euclid Avenue, Suite 1000, Cleveland, OH 44115. 

USE OF THIS SITE SIGNIFIES YOUR AGREEMENT TO THE PRIVACY POLICY. 

Effective Date July 1, 2006.
